export default [
    {
        question: "The following are values of the display property in css except ?",
        options: ["flex", "grid", "none", "inline-box"],
        correctAnswer: "inline-box"
    },
    {
        question: "' * ' is what type of selector ?",
        options: ["descendant selector", "universal selector", "type selector", "child selector"],
        correctAnswer: "universal selector"
    },
    {
        question: "select the correct pair of brackets that houses properties and values in css ?",
        options: ["< >", "( )", "{ }", "[ ]"],
        correctAnswer: "{}"
    },
    {
        question: "':hover' is what type of selector ?",
        options: ["psuedo", "id", "class", "element"],
        correctAnswer: "psuedo"
    },
    {
        question: "how do you select a div tag with a class 'top' in css ?",
        options: ["top", ".top", "*top", "#top"],
        correctAnswer: ".top"
    },
    {
        question: "how do you style the color of a text ?",
        options: ["text-color: #000;", "color: #000;", "txt-color: #000;", "textColor: #000;"],
        correctAnswer: "color: #000"
    },
    {
        question: "the property to specify how flex lines are distributed along the cross axis in a flexbox container ?",
        options: ["margin-content", "flex", "flex-direction", "align-content"],
        correctAnswer: "align-content"
    },
    {
        question: "the property specifies the direction of flexible items ?",
        options: ["flex-content", "place-items", "flex-direction", "place-content"],
        correctAnswer: "flex-direction"
    },
    {
        question: "the property aligns the flexible container's items when the items do not use all available space on the main-axis ?",
        options: ["justify-items", "grid-row-templates", "align-content", "justify-content"],
        correctAnswer: "justify-content"
    },
    {
        question: "length values can be taken from the following css unit properties except ?",
        options: ["cursor", "margin", "padding", "width"],
        correctAnswer: "cursor"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to the font-size of the element ?",
        options: ["rem", "em", "ex", "ch"],
        correctAnswer: "em"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to the x-height of the current font ?",
        options: ["%", "em", "ex", "rem"],
        correctAnswer: "ex"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to the width of the 0 ?",
        options: ["px", "ex", "ch", "rem"],
        correctAnswer: "ch"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to font-size of the root element ?",
        options: ["rem", "vp", "vw", "ch"],
        correctAnswer: "rem"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to 1% of the width of the viewport* ?",
        options: ["ch", "vw", "vs", "vh"],
        correctAnswer: "vw"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to 1% of the height of the viewport* ?",
        options: ["vh", "pm", "ex", "rem"],
        correctAnswer: "vh"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to 1% of viewport's* smaller dimension ?",
        options: ["vwidth", "vmin", "vmid", "vmax"],
        correctAnswer: "vmin"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to 1% of viewport's* larger dimension ?",
        options: ["vmin", "vheight", "vmax", "vmid"],
        correctAnswer: "vmax"
    },
    {
        question: "it is relative to the parent element ?",
        options: ["ch", "ps", "%", "ph"],
        correctAnswer: "%"
    },
    {
        question: "specifies the positioning area of the background images ?",
        options: ["background-origin", "background-position", "background-clip-position", "backgroung-coordinates"],
        correctAnswer: "background-origin"
    }
]